{
  "departments": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Integrated System"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "Software"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "name": "Information Assurance"
    }
  ],
  "employees": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Tran Bao Han",
      "dob": "1980-09-12",
      "gender": "Male",
      "position": "Developer",
      "department": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "Quach Phu Thanh",
      "dob": "1987-01-19",
      "gender": "Female",
      "position": "Developer",
      "department": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "name": "Chu Thanh Quang",
      "dob": "1984-05-23",
      "gender": "Female",
      "position": "Leader",
      "department": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "name": "Trinh Tien Dung",
      "dob": "1990-06-14",
      "gender": "Male",
      "position": "Developer",
      "department": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "name": "Phan Thu Thao",
      "dob": "1990-03-12",
      "gender": "Fe male",
      "position": "Tester",
      "department": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "name": "Nguyen Xuan Quang",
      "dob": "1987-01-19",
      "gender": "Male",
      "position": "Leader",
      "department": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "name": "Trinh Thu Hang",
      "dob": "2000-05-12",
      "gender": "Fe male",
      "position": "Developer",
      "department": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "name": "Tran Hong Quan",
      "dob": "1998-04-16",
      "gender": "Male",
      "position": "Leader",
      "department": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "name": "Pham The Tung",
      "dob": "1984-09-12",
      "gender": "Male",
      "position": "Manager",
      "department": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "name": "Tran Manh Chien",
      "dob": "1983-10-21",
      "gender": "Male",
      "position": "Manager",
      "department": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "Nguyen Hoan",
      "dob": "2024-06-23",
      "gender": "Male",
      "position": "Manger",
      "department": 1,
      "id": 11
    }
  ],

  
    "quiz": {
    "topic": "Javascript",
    "level": "Beginner",
    "totalQuestions": 10,
    "perQuestionScore": 5,
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
        "choices": ["stringify()", "parse()", "convert()", "None of the above"],
        "type": "MCQs",
        "correctAnswer": "stringify()"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
        "choices": ["var", "let", "var and let", "None of the above"],
        "type": "MCQs",
        "correctAnswer": "var and let"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
        "choices": ["document.write()", "console.log()", "window.alert", "All of the above"],
        "type": "MCQs",
        "correctAnswer": "All of the above"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
        "choices": ["const", "var", "let", "constant"],
        "type": "MCQs",
        "correctAnswer": "const"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What is the output of the following code: console.log(typeof undefined);",
        "choices": ["undefined", "null", "object", "string"],
        "type": "MCQs",
        "correctAnswer": "undefined"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which operator is used to concatenate strings in Javascript?",
        "choices": ["+", "&", ".", ","],
        "type": "MCQs",
        "correctAnswer": "+"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What does NaN stand for in Javascript?",
        "choices": ["Not a Null", "Not a Number", "Null and Notable", "None of the above"],
        "type": "MCQs",
        "correctAnswer": "Not a Number"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "How do you declare a function in Javascript?",
        "choices": ["function myFunction()", "myFunction()", "function = myFunction()", "None of the above"],
        "type": "MCQs",
        "correctAnswer": "function myFunction()"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Which method removes the last element from an array and returns that element in Javascript?",
        "choices": ["pop()", "shift()", "slice()", "None of the above"],
        "type": "MCQs",
        "correctAnswer": "pop()"
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which method adds one or more elements to the end of an array and returns the new length of the array in Javascript?",
        "choices": ["unshift()", "push()", "splice()", "None of the above"],
        "type": "MCQs",
        "correctAnswer": "push()"
      }
      ]
    
  }
}